<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WasteNot</string>
    <string name="capture_button">Capture</string>
    <string name="classify_static">Your waste is most likely:</string>
    <string name="classify_default">Error</string>
    <string name="classify_cardboard">Cardboard</string>
    <string name="classify_glass">Glass</string>
    <string name="classify_metal">Metal</string>
    <string name="classify_paper">Paper</string>
    <string name="classify_plastic">Plastic</string>
    <string name="classify_trash">Trash</string>
    <string name="classify_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="result_positive">Recyclable</string>
    <string name="result_negative">Not recyclable</string>
    <string name="explanation_default">Aw, this wasn\'t supposed to happen! If you\'re seeing this,
                                        either the server is down or there was an error with the app
                                        displaying the result. Please try again at another time.</string>
    <string name="explanation_cardboard">You can recycle this, but there is one condition; soiled
                                        cardboard goes in the garbage. If this is a pizza or donut
                                        box, for example. the grease makes recycling impossible.
                                        Otherwise, just be sure to shake away any food crumbs, remove
                                        packing tape and any plastic liners, and flatten the cardboard
                                        if it\'s a box, and in the recycling it goes!</string>
    <string name="explanation_glass">This is most likely a glass container, like a bottle, mug, or jar,
                                    which you can basically recycle as is. Dump any residual food or
                                    oil into the compost and give the glass a quick rinse.
                                    If there\'s a metal cap or wine cork
                                    on top, you can recycle that, but it must be removed from the
                                    container first.</string>
    <string name="explanation_metal">This one\'s an easy one! All metals are infinitely recyclable,
                                    INCLUDING clean aluminum foil, with the sole exception of aerosol
                                    cans that are partially full. Lightly rinse the object with water
                                    and you\'re good to go.</string>
    <string name="explanation_paper">Virtually all forms of paper can be recycled! Newspapers,
                                    sticky notes, glossy magazines, colored paper, you name it. Make
                                    sure the paper is dry, and metal parts like staples and paper clips
                                    can be left on, although reusing paper clips is advisable. If
                                    your paper contains sensitive information, consider covering it
                                    with Sharpie instead of shredding it, which makes the paper last
                                    a shorter time due to the smaller wood fibers.</string>
    <string name="explanation_plastic">Hard plastic, like jugs, plastic bottles, and salad containers, are recyclable.
                                        Lightly rinse out the contents and put the plastic cap back
                                        on; it actually makes recyclers\' lives easier! Plastic wraps,
                                        films, and bags are trickier. To recycle these, you have to
                                        take them to storefront recycling bins at your nearest Walmart
                                        or Target.</string>
    <string name="explanation_trash">Sometimes there\'s just nothing you can do! Find the nearest
                                    landfill bin and chuck this in."</string>
    <string name="explanation_unknown">Sorry, our app was stumped on this one! Make sure the object
                                        takes up the whole camera frame, no more, no less, and put
                                        it on a well-lit, white surface for better results.</string>
</resources>
